

Mean Developer seeking assignment in Software Application Development, Software Development, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, Software Design, Workflow Architecture, Software Testing, PHP, Node Js, Web API, MySQL Server, Javascript, Rest Web Services



Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 6 Month(s) Current Designation: Mean Developer

Current Company: Chetu India Pvt. Ltd. Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Electronics/Telecommunication] Current Location: Noida

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Delhi / NCR, Mumbai Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Mean Developer, Software Developer, Software Application Development, Software Development, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, Software Design, Workflow Architecture, Software Testing, PHP, Node Js, Web

API, MySQL Server, Javascript, Rest Web Services

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

I Have 4.6 years of experience as a Software Developer in JavaScript, Angular 2, 6, 8, 9 and implementation of web and client server applications using PHP and Express.js.

Experience in design and development of applications using PHP, Node Js, Web API, MySQL Server, Javascript . Hands on Experience in Rest Web Services with laravel Framework And Express Js.

Good Experience in developing the Single Page Applications using Angular 2.

Experience on working with Custom Directives, Components, Services, filters modules of Angular 2.

Good understanding of Model View Controller design patterns.

Experience in system analysis, design, workflow architecture, development, testing and maintenance of web based applications.

Ability to work independently and as a part of the team with Excellent Technical, Analytical and Communication

Work on both large scale and small-scale projects both independently and as a part of a team.

Work Experience

Chetu India Pvt. Ltd. as Mean Developer Jun 2019 to Till Date

Mobzway Technologies LLP as Angular Developer Aug 2017 to Jun 2019

RAD Techno Solutions Pvt. Ltd as PHP Web Developer Jun 2016 to Jul 2017

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics/Telecommunication) from M.A.I.E.T., Jaipur, Rajasthan (RTU Kota). in 2015

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
PHP, Node Js, Oops, Angular 2, 6, 8, 9			
Web API			
HTML5, JavaScript, TypeScript,PHP,NodeJS			
MySql Server, MongoDB			
Laravel, Angular, express Js			
Visual studio code, Sublime-Text			
Code sniffer, TS lint, JS Hint			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time